[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Joe Dirt, who plays Robbie, the guy who always kicks up dirt in Joes face with his car?", "correct_answer": "Kid Rock", "incorrect_answers": ["Peter DeLuise", "Chris Farley", "Eminem"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The USA is divided into states. England is divided into counties. Which country is divided into departments?", "correct_answer": "France", "incorrect_answers": ["India", "Ireland", "Taiwan"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The French Revolution broke out in 1789.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the total collection of traits that determine the physical and behavioral aspects of an organism called?", "correct_answer": "Phenotype", "incorrect_answers": ["Alleles", "DNA Markers", "Genotype"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following is a major source of iron, which helps carry oxygen to the tissues?", "correct_answer": "Raisins", "incorrect_answers": ["Broccoli", "Lemons", "Tomatoes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What color is a John Deere tractor?", "correct_answer": "Green", "incorrect_answers": ["Red", "Blue", "Black"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many planets are in the Solar System?", "correct_answer": "8", "incorrect_answers": ["10", "15", "12"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which two actors have played the Batman villain, Two-Face?", "correct_answer": "Tommy Lee Jones, Aaron Eckhart", "incorrect_answers": ["Jack Nicholson, Tommy Lee Jones", "Danny DeVito, Jim Carrey", "Aaron Eckhart, Jim Carrey"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which skeletal muscle raises or throws back the shoulders, assists in moving the head to one side or another, and helps hold the head erect?", "correct_answer": "Trapezius", "incorrect_answers": ["Platysma", "Latissimus dorsi", "Sternocleidomastoid"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Dactyloscopy, a technique perfected by anthropologist Juan Vucetichs, studies what?", "correct_answer": "Fingerprints", "incorrect_answers": ["The shape of human head", "Flightless birds", "Land dinosaurs"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following actors has NOT portrayed the Frankenstein monster?", "correct_answer": "Michael Landon", "incorrect_answers": ["Randy Quaid", "Christopher Lee", "Robert DeNiro"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Dr. Susan Calvin, the main character of many short stories, is a robopsychologist.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]